I know it all
난 다 알아요
Do they really trust you?
그 사람들이 정말로 당신을 신뢰하는 걸까요?
That's good
좋아요
can say that
라고 말할 수 있다
My prison meals these days have not been in vain.
요즘 제가 감옥에서 먹은 식사는 헛되지 않았습니다.
I feel wronged to you
나는 당신에게 억울함을 느낀다
Not wronged
잘못한 것이 아니다
I found it
찾았어요
I am now
나는 지금
Just professional cannon fodder
그냥 전문 대포 사료
but
하지만
I'm really happy this time
이번에는 정말 행복해요
As long as you can successfully land
성공적으로 착륙할 수 있는 한
It's worth it even if I'm broken to pieces
조각조각 부서져도 가치가 있어
Zicheng
자성
Thank you
감사합니다
Why are you so polite to me?
왜 나한테 그렇게 예의바르게 대하는 거야?
Have we been there for a long time?
우리 거기에 오랫동안 있었나요?
nothing like now
지금과 같은 건 아무것도 없어
Stay together
함께있어
yes
예
but
하지만
This thing
이 것
Getting better little by little
조금씩 나아지고 있어요
Later
나중에
the time we spend together
우리가 함께 보내는 시간
there will be many
많을 것이다
But
하지만
But I'm leaving Jinhai
하지만 난 진하이를 떠난다
where to
어디로
As soon as Zhou Zhe transferred me,
Zhou Zhe가 나를 옮기자마자,
The operating company of Agent Game
Agent Game 운영회사
Make me the game director
나를 게임 디렉터로 만들어 주세요
so suddenly
그래서 갑자기
If you want to get his evidence
그 사람의 증거를 얻고 싶다면
this is an opportunity
이건 기회야
no
아니요
you can't go
넌 갈 수 없어
Too dangerous
너무 위험해
Didn’t you just say that?
방금 그렇게 말하지 않았나요?
this could be me
이게 나일 수도 있어
Last chance to go ashore
해변으로 갈 수 있는 마지막 기회
It's worth it to be broken into pieces
조각조각 쪼개져도 아깝다
That
저것
Have you thought it through?
생각해 보셨나요?
Think it through
생각해 보세요
That
저것
will you go with me
나와 함께 갈래?
I
나
Do you need me to go with you?
내가 당신과 함께 가야 합니까?
I'm teasing you
나는 당신을 놀리는 중입니다
Are you kidding me?
농담하는 거야?
this is myself
이건 나야
Things that need to be faced
직면해야 할 것들
It has nothing to do with you
그것은 당신과 아무 관련이 없습니다
I go
나 간다
Yao Yao
야오야오
What about you?
당신은 어때요?
When you lie
거짓말을 할 때
I just like to pick my fingernails
나는 단지 손톱을 고르는 것을 좋아한다
You must pay attention to this
이 점을 주의하셔야 합니다.
any detail
어떤 세부 사항이라도
will betray you
당신을 배신할 것이다
You won't do it for no reason
아무 이유 없이 그런 짓은 안 할 거야
Tell me to accompany you
같이 가자고 말해요
If we go together
우리가 함께 가면
If I guess correctly
내 추측이 맞다면
i should be you
내가 너여야 해
Go back as a bargaining chip
협상 카드로 돌아가세요
Can they offer such conditions?
그런 조건을 제시할 수 있나요?
Just show
그냥 보여줘
They don't fully trust you yet
그들은 아직 당신을 완전히 신뢰하지 않습니다
I went
나는 갔다
Can help you gain their trust
그들의 신뢰를 얻는 데 도움이 될 수 있습니다
But you know it
하지만 당신은 그것을 알고
this is a trap
이건 함정이야
If you go there, you'll be free to eat mermaid meat.
거기 가면 인어고기를 마음껏 먹을 수 있어요.
If I don't go
내가 가지 않으면
The man who lets people eat meat
남에게 고기를 먹게 하는 남자
it's you
너야
Yewu has already agreed
Yewu는 이미 동의했습니다.
my request
내 요청
After getting the HY106 data
HY106 데이터를 얻은 후
Arrange for me and Boss Zhang
나와 Boss Zhang을 위해 준비하십시오.
leave together
함께 떠나다
leave
떠나다
I thought
나는 생각했다
You just go through Boss Zhang
그냥 Boss Zhang을 거쳐가세요
Come and investigate the secrets hidden in Jinhai
오셔서 진하이에 숨겨진 비밀을 조사해보세요
spy network
스파이 네트워크
why do you want to leave
왜 떠나고 싶어?
The night fog is now
밤안개는 지금
Starting to doubt me
날 의심하기 시작해
let me risk
위험을 감수하자
Take this experimental data
이 실험 데이터를 가지고
obviously not them
분명 그 사람들은 아니겠지
best choice
최선의 선택
I do not have either
나도 없어
One hundred percent sure
백퍼센트 확실해
But they still let me do it
하지만 그들은 여전히 ​​내가 그렇게 하도록 허락해 주었어요
Then they still have a backup plan
그렇다면 여전히 백업 계획이 있습니다
In the hands of Boss Zhang
장보스의 손에
One more trump card
트럼프 카드 한 장 더
Just inside the Bio Group
바이오그룹 내부
His actions are more reliable
그의 행동이 더 믿음직스러워요
so let you go
그러니 널 보내줘
It's their usual trick
그게 그 사람들의 평소 속임수야
The plank road was repaired in the open, but Chencang was buried in the dark
판자 길은 공개적으로 수리되었지만 Chencang은 어둠 속에 묻혔습니다.
That's right
좋아요
Thanks
감사해요
You go to Yewu to work as an undercover agent
당신은 잠복요원으로 일하기 위해 예우에 갑니다.
It's impossible
그것은 불가능
why
왜
You are a national security officer
당신은 국가 안보 책임자입니다
How can they trust you?
그들이 당신을 어떻게 믿을 수 있습니까?
You are the biggest to them
당신은 그들에게 가장 큰 존재입니다
Utilization value
활용 가치
That means you stay in the National Security Bureau
그건 당신이 국가 안보국에 남아 있다는 뜻이에요
once you leave
일단 떠나면
You have no value anymore
당신은 더 이상 가치가 없습니다
How could they take you in?
그들이 어떻게 당신을 받아들일 수 있었나요?
It's too risky for you to do this
네가 이런 짓을 하는 건 너무 위험해
you have a point
당신은 일리가 있어요
But for the mission
하지만 임무를 위해서는
i must take risk
나는 위험을 감수해야 해
No, I have to talk to him.
아뇨, 그 사람이랑 얘기 좀 해야 해요
Don't make trouble for others
남에게 폐를 끼치지 마세요
Can you believe me once?
한 번만 믿어주실 수 있나요?
I can't die
난 죽을 수 없어
Look, are you sad now?
봐, 지금 슬프지?
what is this
이게 뭔가요
These were all given by Zicheng
이것들은 모두 Zicheng이 준 것입니다.
Look like
처럼 생겼어
unlike
같지 않은
these things
이런 일
Just help me keep it safe first.
먼저 안전하게 지킬 수 있도록 도와주세요.
OK
좋아요
I'm waiting for you to come back
나는 당신이 돌아 오기를 기다리고 있습니다
Give it back to you
다시 돌려줘
Thank you, Officer Wu
고마워요, 우 경관님
You're welcome
천만에요
Section Chief Gao
가오 과장
I don't even remember
기억도 안나
Last time I came to the beach
저번에 해변에 왔을 때
when is it
언제야?
Often things around us
우리 주변에 흔히 있는 일들
Most easily ignored
가장 쉽게 무시됨
you have to do me a favor
나한테 부탁 좀 해줘야 해
What are you busy with?
무슨 일로 바쁜가요?
i need one
하나 필요해
The latest HY106 data
최신 HY106 데이터
Ye Wu asked you to do it
예우가 해달라고 했어
Finish this time
이번에는 마무리
I'm ready to leave
난 떠날 준비가 됐어
where to
어디로
have no idea
전혀 모른다
I'm leaving anyway
어차피 난 떠날 거야
I also decided
나도 결심했다
I'm going with Yao Yao
야오야오랑 갈래
Zicheng
자성
You don't have to go with me
나랑 같이 갈 필요는 없어
you don't want
당신은 원하지 않는다
Shall I go with you?
나도 같이 갈까?
this is too dangerous
이건 너무 위험해
Isn't it dangerous for you to go?
가면 위험하지 않아?
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
I am now a professional cannon fodder
나는 이제 전문 대포 사료입니다
if i don't leave
내가 떠나지 않으면
They won't trust you either
그 사람들도 당신을 믿지 않을 거예요
Is it right
맞아
So comfortable
너무 편해요
do you remember
기억 나니
When we were kids
우리가 어렸을 때
This is my favorite time to go swimming
이때가 내가 수영하러 가기 가장 좋아하는 시간이다
I can also go into the water now
나도 이제 물에 들어갈 수 있다
Do you really want to do it?
정말로 하고 싶나요?
Leave him
그를 놔둬 라
He's like that
그 사람이 그러더라고
Do whatever comes to mind
생각나는 대로 하세요
Brother Tianyang
텐양 형제
really want him
정말로 그를 원해
come with me
날 따라와
if he doesn't go
그 사람이 안 가면
All efforts are wasted
모든 노력이 낭비된다
really dangerous
정말 위험해
when necessary
필요할 땐
It requires sacrifice
희생이 필요하다
But that's your brother
하지만 그 사람은 네 동생이야
this is the struggle
이것이 투쟁이다
Now that you have chosen to join
이제 가입을 선택하셨으니
That requires wisdom and courage
그러기 위해서는 지혜와 용기가 필요하다
to fight
싸우기 위해서
rather than shrinking back
뒤로 물러나는 것보다
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
Someone will be responsible for his safety
누군가는 그의 안전을 책임질 것이다
come
오다
Come on, Gao Tianyang
자, 가오텐양
Coming
오는
Come down and play for a while
내려와서 잠시 놀다
It’s time to eat
이제 먹을 시간이다
It’s time to eat, it’s time to eat
밥 먹을 시간이야, 밥 먹을 시간이야
No rest at noon
정오에 쉬지 않음
Is it noon?
정오인가요?
It's almost half past twelve
거의 12시 반이네
You said you, old comrade
말했잖아, 옛 동지여
We can’t just focus on construction.
건설에만 집중할 수는 없습니다.
You also have to pay attention to your health
건강에도 유의하셔야 합니다
There is another meeting in the afternoon
오후에 또 회의가 있어요
No meal at noon
정오에는 식사가 없습니다.
eat
먹다
Xiao Liu went to buy it
Xiao Liu가 그것을 사러 갔다
Fine
괜찮은
Then I won't bother you
그럼 귀찮게 하지 않을게
The leader is working
리더가 일하고 있어요
I'll call my brother back tonight
오늘 밤에 내 동생에게 다시 전화할게
Let's have a meal together
같이 밥 먹자
OK
좋아요
Fortunately, I have nothing to do in the afternoon
다행히 오후에는 할 일이 없어서
What to eat
무엇을 먹을까
I'll go buy it in advance in the afternoon
오후에 미리 사러 갈게요
Don't worry about it
걱정하지 마세요
The two of us will do it for you
우리 둘이서 해줄게
I will honor and honor you well.
나는 당신을 잘 존경하고 존중할 것입니다.
I feel like this attitude is not quite right.
이런 태도는 옳지 않다고 생각합니다.
I thought you came to me
나한테 온 줄 알았는데
Is there some bad news to announce?
발표할 나쁜 소식이 있나요?
or
또는
Just come to borrow money from me
그냥 나한테 돈 빌리러 오세요
Why am I in your heart
나는 왜 당신의 마음 속에 있습니까?
This image is so unbearable
이미지이건 참을 수 없을 정도로
Anyway, if you
어쨌든 만약 당신이
If you really want to help me
정말로 나를 돕고 싶다면
Then I won’t refuse
그럼 거절 안 할게
You boy, you
너, 너
You two are Lao Huang's sons, right?
너희 둘은 라오황의 아들이지?
When I was a kid, I followed behind
어렸을 때 뒤를 따라가던
It's so big now
지금은 너무 커졌어
Okay, it looks good.
좋아요, 좋아 보이네요.
When I said frying fish
생선튀김이라고 했더니
You have to watch it carefully
주의깊게 살펴보셔야 해요
Don't burn it, I tell you
태우지 마세요.
If you can do it, come
할 수 있으면 오세요
That's not okay
그건 안 돼
Today we agreed that you two will do it
오늘 우리는 너희 둘이 하기로 합의했다
I eat ready-made
나는 즉석에서 먹는다.
brother
형제
Look at my fish
내 물고기 좀 봐
Isn't it a bit too much?
좀 너무한거 아냐?
uncle
삼촌
Come, come, come and see
와라 와라 와 보라
Zicheng’s fried fish is so awesome
Zicheng의 생선튀김은 정말 맛있어요
Come on come on
어서 어서
Why is it so delicious?
왜 이렇게 맛있나요?
It won’t burn after it’s fried.
튀긴 후에는 타지 않습니다.
What did I just say?
내가 방금 뭐라고 말했지?
Mixed up like this
이렇게 섞어서
How can we still eat it, you say?
어떻게 아직도 그걸 먹을 수 있냐고요?
never mind
괜찮아요
The pan is sticky
냄비가 끈적끈적해요
We can go out to eat
우리는 나가서 먹을 수 있어요
Go out to eat
먹으러 가자
What time is it?
지금 몇 시지?
There are queues everywhere now
이제 어디든 줄이 늘어서 있어요
Wait until he doesn't starve to death
굶어죽지 않을 때까지 기다리세요
Don't, don't, don't worry
하지마, 하지마, 걱정하지마
I think of a way
방법이 생각나는데
Think of a way, think of a way
방법을 생각해 보세요, 방법을 생각해 보세요
Isn’t this dish a good cut?
이 요리는 잘 먹히지 않나요?
Then eat hot pot instead and that's it.
그럼 대신 냄비를 먹으면 끝이에요.
high high
높음 높음
come on! Come on
어서! 어서
come on, come on, come on
어서, 어서, 어서
Gao Tianyang Gao Tianyang
가오텐양 가오텐양
Always the last one
항상 마지막
How about it
어때요?
Accept or not
수락 여부
I said you didn't mean it
난 당신이 그럴 의도가 아니라고 말했어요
Give me some water
물 좀 주세요
No, no, no
아니, 아니
Not this time, really not this time
이번에는 안돼, 정말 이번엔 안돼
The sword is not old yet
칼은 아직 늙지 않았어
Invincibility is so lonely
무적은 너무 외로워
You are still a master
당신은 여전히 ​​​​마스터입니다
Even I can't play it
심지어 나는 그것을 재생할 수 없습니다
He just has good hands
그 사람 손이 좋을 뿐이야
drink drink drink
마셔 마셔 마셔
Come, come, have a drink
자, 자, 한잔 마셔라
A cup of honor yellow
경로노란 한잔
do it again do it again do it again
다시 해 다시 해 다시 해
One more round, come on, come on
한 바퀴만 더, 어서, 어서
Uncle, let’s go first
아저씨, 먼저 가세요
Slow down on the road
도로에서는 속도를 늦추세요
Go back and rest early
돌아가서 일찍 쉬세요
What's going on? This is
무슨 일이에요?
You also give Lao Huang a hug
라오황도 안아주세요
What's going on today?
오늘 무슨 일이야?
It's like a farewell ceremony
마치 이별식 같아
This hug
이 포옹
It’s etiquette between normal people
보통 사람들 사이의 예절이잖아
Later
나중에
We have to be normal too
우리도 평범해야 해
Okay, okay, you have many tricks
알았어 알았어, 넌 트릭이 많아
let's go
갑시다
You go back
너는 돌아가라
You go quickly
빨리 가세요
OK OK OK
오케이 오케이 오케이
I won’t send it to you anymore
이제 너한테는 안 보내줄게
Take care of yourself
몸 조심하세요
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
Go to Yao Yao's place
야오야오의 집으로 가세요
action tomorrow
내일 행동
Nothing can go wrong
아무것도 잘못될 수 없어
Someone will be watching us
누군가 우리를 지켜보고 있을 거예요
clear
분명한
Came back so early
너무 일찍 돌아왔어
I've just finished eating
이제 막 식사를 마쳤어요
What do you want to eat
너 뭐 먹고 싶니
I'll do it for you
내가 해줄게
No
아니요
when to act
언제 행동해야 하는가
tomorrow
내일
so fast
너무 빨라
I'm really reluctant to give up
정말 포기하기 싫어요
I will leave with you
나는 당신과 함께 떠날 것이다
Mr. Yu and I have finished talking.
유 씨와 저는 이야기를 마쳤습니다.
Have you considered
고려해 보셨나요?
What
무엇
After going abroad
해외로 나간 후
What do you want to do
뭐하고 싶어
what do you think i can do
내가 뭘 할 수 있을 것 같아?
be my partner
내 파트너가 되어줘
I don't want to be
나는되고 싶지 않아
Another Xiao Yi
또 다른 샤오이
Will not
하지 않을 것이다
you are so smart
당신은 정말 똑똑해요
Yes
예
I can play the spy game
스파이 게임을 할 수 있어요
I heard about that game
그 게임에 대해 들었어
Especially profitable
특히 수익성이 높음
you don't need to play games
게임을 할 필요는 없어
you are already one
당신은 이미 하나입니다
Very good agent
아주 좋은 에이전트
There will be many companies hiring you
당신을 채용하는 회사가 많이 있을 것입니다.
Do you think Ye Wu can take me in?
Ye Wu가 나를 받아 들일 수 있다고 생각하세요?
Who knows
누가 알아
Let’s talk about it after we get out.
나가서 얘기하자.
You should pack your things first
먼저 물건을 챙겨야 해요
Don't wait for me at home tomorrow
내일 집에서 기다리지 마세요
Why
왜
Tomorrow's action is an adventure
내일의 행동은 모험이다
If I'm going to get caught
내가 잡힐 거라면
Just escape by yourself
그냥 혼자서 탈출해라
you were caught
당신은 잡혔어요
If I confess, I can be imprisoned for a few years less
자백하면 징역 몇년 단축 가능
Pointless
무의미한
To me it's do or die
나에게 있어 그것은 죽느냐 아니면 죽느냐의 문제야
no retreat
후퇴 없음
Don't be too nice to me
나에게 너무 친절하게 대하지 마세요.
i will disappoint you
나는 당신을 실망시킬 것이다
I didn't expect it
나는 그것을 기대하지 않았다
what can you give me
나에게 무엇을 줄 수 있나요?
That's good
좋아요
can i ask a personal question
개인적인 질문 하나 해도 될까요
What
무엇
do you have a family
당신, 가족이 있나요
I only have myself
나에겐 나밖에 없다
This is the emotional bond we have in this business
이것이 바로 이 사업에서 우리가 갖고 있는 감정적 유대감입니다.
Will mislead my judgment
내 판단을 오해하게 될 거야
Then why did you choose one?
그렇다면 왜 하나를 선택했나요?
Such a difficult road
이렇게 힘든 길
Then why do you want to be a national security officer?
그렇다면 왜 국가안보관이 되고 싶은가?
avoiding problem
문제 회피
Tell me first
먼저 말해봐
let me think
생각해볼게
Do you want to answer your question?
귀하의 질문에 답변하시겠습니까?
university graduate
대학 졸업
Apply for national security
국가 안보 신청
Passed the training
교육을 통과했습니다.
Then take up the job
그럼 일을 맡아
It's that simple
그렇게 간단해요
I don't want to know
알고 싶지 않아요
Guoan recruitment process
궈안 채용 프로세스
What I'm asking is
내가 묻는 것은
Why are you
너는 왜
To be a national security officer
국가안보요원이 되려면
My parents were in a fire
부모님이 불에 탔어요
died accidentally
우연히 사망
And that accident
그리고 그 사고
that's because
그것은 ~ 때문에
Caused by spies stealing secrets
스파이가 비밀을 훔쳐서 발생
I thought I was going to hear a
나는 어떤 말을 듣게 될 것이라고 생각했다.
How ambitious
얼마나 야심찬지
and pursuit story
그리고 추적 이야기
Unexpectedly, it was also hatred
의외로 증오이기도 했어
This is not revenge
이건 복수가 아니야
The person who died is no longer there
돌아가신 분은 이제 없어요
but living people
하지만 살아있는 사람들
I must protect
나는 보호해야 한다
I'm done
난 끝났어
Are you satisfied with my answer?
내 대답에 만족하시나요?
When I was young
내가 어렸을 때
Maybe worse than you
어쩌면 너보다 더 나쁠 수도 있어
little mute
작은 음소거
Come this way
이쪽으로 오세요
Look at the children in our courtyard
우리 마당에 있는 아이들을 보세요
They're all down there
다들 저쪽에 있어
little mute
작은 음소거
Then I'll go and get busy first.
그럼 먼저 가서 바쁘게 지내겠습니다.
If you don’t cry or make trouble, you’re a fool
울지 않고 말썽 피우지 않으면 바보야
cry
울다
little mute
작은 음소거
Really annoying
정말 짜증나
Don't cry or make trouble
울지 말고, 문제를 일으키지 마세요.
know why
왜 그런지 안다
will i choose you
내가 당신을 선택할 것인가?
Because there is hatred in your eyes
네 눈에는 증오가 담겨있으니까
like now
지금처럼
Even in desperate situation
절망적인 상황에서도
Still want to bite the enemy back?
아직도 적을 물어뜯고 싶나요?
Although your eyes are good
눈은 좋아도
but sometimes
하지만 가끔은
An act of overestimation
과대평가하는 행위
It will make you suffer
당신을 고통스럽게 만들 거예요
Do you still hate them?
아직도 그들을 싫어하시나요?
Remember this feeling
이 느낌을 기억해
hatred
증오
Sometimes it makes people stronger
때론 사람을 더 강하게 만들어주죠
don't ask me
나에게 묻지 마세요
will i take you somewhere
내가 당신을 어딘가로 데려갈까요?
where to
어디로
It's better than here now
지금 여기보다 나아요
You will live here from now on
너는 이제부터 여기서 살 것이다.
Get along well with everyone
모두와 잘 지내요
What are you doing
뭐하세요
release
풀어 주다
Okay, okay, okay
알았어 알았어 알았어
let go
놓아줘
Let go
가자
Excuting an order
주문 실행
don't want
원하지 않는다
Don't don't
하지 마십시오
Where are you taking her?
그녀를 어디로 데려가나요?
accept punishment
처벌을 받아들이다
She needs to calm down and think carefully
그녀는 진정하고 신중하게 생각해야 합니다
Why did she lose?
그녀는 왜 졌습니까?
Do you want to have a fight too?
너도 한번 싸워볼까?
One is eliminated every week
매주 한 명씩 탈락
new ones coming in
새로운 것들이 들어오고 있어
Replace the one who was eliminated
제거된 사람을 교체하세요.
I don't want to be eliminated
난 탈락하고 싶지 않아
I don't want to either
나도 그러고 싶지 않아
I didn't know until later
나중에까지 몰랐어요
that place
그 장소
It's a spy school, right?
스파이 학교 맞죠?
They recruit from all over
여기저기서 모집해요
Children of school age
학령기 아동
Raised since childhood, systematic training
어릴 때부터 키워온 체계적인 훈련
Then
그 다음에
and then transported to various countries
그리고 여러 나라로 운송됩니다.
Become a real spy
진짜 스파이가 되어보세요
what you just said
방금 말한 것
Is it training?
훈련인가요?
almost every week
거의 매주
People keep being sent away
사람들이 계속 쫓겨나고 있어요
Someone will disappear suddenly
누군가 갑자기 사라질 것이다.
Some people can't stand the torture
어떤 사람들은 고문을 참지 못해요
suicide
자살
But soon
하지만 곧
There will be new children
새로운 아이들이 생길 거예요
fill in
채우다
cruel
잔혹한
indifferent
무관심한
ruthless
무자비한
Mission first
임무 우선
through training one at a time
한 번에 하나씩 훈련을 통해
Kill all normal emotions
정상적인 감정을 모두 죽여라
Leave only what is needed
꼭 필요한 것만 남겨두세요
But it's okay
하지만 괜찮습니다
I made at least one friend
나는 적어도 한 명의 친구를 사귀었다
only friend
유일한 친구
that boy
그 소년
It's Ran Fei, right?
란페이 맞죠?
So you are so sure
그러니 당신은 확신해요
He won't betray me
그 사람은 나를 배신하지 않을 거야
You believe it
당신은 그것을 믿습니다
No, Section Chief Gao
아니, 가오 과장
Such a vulgar story
이런 저속한 이야기
You believe it too
너도 그걸 믿어
I just like clichéd stories
난 그냥 진부한 이야기를 좋아하는 것 같아
Is there any follow-up?
후속조치가 있나요?
story without ending
끝나지 않는 이야기
That's the most perfect
그게 가장 완벽해
According to your story
당신의 이야기에 따르면
I won't be
나는 그렇지 않을 것이다
Be the next one to be eliminated
다음으로 제거될 사람이 되세요
As long as one person is still valuable
한 사람이 여전히 소중한 한
won't be eliminated
제거되지 않습니다
It seems I still have value
난 아직 가치가 있는 것 같아
certainly
틀림없이
So keep it
그러니 유지하세요
own value
자신의 가치
Don't do stupid things
어리석은 짓은 하지 마세요
You do it
당신은 그것을 할
Look at me
날 봐
what does it feel like
어떤 느낌이야?
It's like a lifetime ago
마치 평생 전과 같아
Zicheng
자성
I think you should stay
내 생각엔 네가 머물러야 할 것 같아
Have you ever thought about it
그것에 대해 생각해 본 적이 있나요?
If Brother Tianyang goes
천양 형제가 가면
You went too
너도 갔어
What about uncle?
삼촌은 어때요?
It’s not like I won’t come back if I go.
가면 다시 안 올 것 같지는 않은데.
But even I went
그런데 나도 갔어.
Don't even know what to face
무엇을 직면해야 할지조차 모르겠어
What's more, it's you
게다가 너야
so
그래서
That makes it even more necessary for me to go
그래서 내가 가야 할 곳이 더욱 필요해졌어
I have to protect you
나는 당신을 보호해야
Protect
보호하다
How do you protect me?
나를 어떻게 보호합니까?
The two of us were alone there
거기엔 우리 둘만 있었어
What we have to face is
우리가 직면해야 할 것은
entire espionage organization
간첩조직 전체
You can't even protect yourself
넌 너 자신도 보호할 수 없어
What are you doing to protect me?
나를 보호하기 위해 무엇을 하고 있나요?
Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉
you will always be like this
너는 언제나 이럴 거야
feel good about yourself
너 자신에 대해 기분이 좋아
But you never know
하지만 넌 절대 모르지
after you pass
합격한 후에
What dangers will you face?
어떤 위험에 직면하게 될까요?
Yao Yao
야오야오
It's not like I haven't experienced it before
예전에 경험해보지 못한 것 같지는 않은데
Wouldn't they take me too?
나도 데려가지 않을까?
Nothing wrong?
아무 잘못 없음?
I know you are comforting me
네가 나를 위로하고 있다는 걸 알아
But now that you've escaped
하지만 이제 당신은 탈출했으니까
Just don't get involved anymore, okay?
더 이상 관여하지 마세요, 알았죠?
So I can't let you
그래서 난 당신을 보낼 수 없습니다
Go alone
혼자 가다
if you can
당신이 할 수 있다면
someone i'd rather go to
내가 가고 싶은 사람
it's me
나야
It's all doomed
다 운명이야
Now things have developed like this
이제 상황이 이렇게 발전했어요
Brother Tianyang and I must leave
Tianyang 형제와 나는 떠나야 해
But you are different
하지만 당신은 달라요
You still have a home
아직 집이 있잖아
And uncle
그리고 삼촌
You can still stay in Jinhai
진하이에 계속 머물 수 있어요
fulfill your dream
당신의 꿈을 이루세요
If you have a chance
기회가 있다면
we can meet again
우리는 다시 만날 수 있어요
No but me
아니 나만 빼고
Stop talking
그만 얘기해
Listen to me this time
이번엔 내 말 좀 들어봐
Just let me beg you, okay?
그냥 부탁 좀 할게요, 알았죠?
OK
좋아요
the time we can stay together
우리가 함께 있을 수 있는 시간
Running out
소진하다
Don't waste this time anymore
더 이상 이 시간을 낭비하지 마세요
in some unnecessary
일부 불필요한
Things are over
상황은 끝났어
We've been together for so long
우리는 너무 오랫동안 함께 있었어
Not one yet
아직 하나도 없음
What about the official group photo?
공식 단체 사진은 어떤가요?
Yes
예
But it's so late
하지만 너무 늦었어
No place to take pictures
사진 찍을 곳이 없네
Not always
항상 그런 것은 아니다
look
바라보다
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
there
거기
Zicheng
자성
Where are you taking me?
나를 어디로 데려가나요?
let's get married
결혼합시다
Right here
바로 여기에
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
Come
오다
Wait for me here
여기서 기다려주세요
this this
이
Am I wearing this?
내가 이걸 입고 있는 걸까?
Very strange
아주 이상한
Not surprising at all
전혀 놀라운 일이 아니다
very beautiful
매우 아름다운
real
진짜
correct
옳은
You just talked to them
당신은 방금 그들과 이야기를 나눴습니다.
What have you said?
당신은 무엇을 말했습니까?
I'll tell them
내가 그들에게 말해줄게
I want to be with me
나는 나와 함께 있고 싶다
The one you love proposes
사랑하는 사람이 프러포즈를 한다
Full of lies
거짓말이 가득해
I really think so
정말 그런 것 같아요
look
바라보다
I even prepared the ring
반지도 준비했어요
Okay, stop making trouble
알았어, 그만 괴롭혀
Let's take a photo
사진을 찍자
Just leave it as a souvenir
그냥 기념품으로 남겨두세요
Just the two of us
단지 우리의 두
at this moment
지금이 순간
It's enough to be together
함께 있으면 충분해
bring it on
그것을 가져오다
Look here, you two.
여기 보세요, 두 분.
good very good
좋아 아주 좋아
good
좋은
Let's make out
의 밖으로 만들어 보자
Okay, one more
알았어, 하나 더
good
좋은
thank you
감사합니다
I can't move this
이거 옮길 수가 없어
You can't move either
너도 움직일 수 없어
I can't do this anymore
더 이상은 할 수 없어
what happened
무슨 일이에요
our firewall
우리 방화벽
being attacked
공격을 받고
The system has activated an emergency state
시스템이 비상 상태를 활성화했습니다
Turn off the Internet immediately
즉시 인터넷을 꺼주세요
lead
선두
This is a malicious attack
이는 악의적인 공격입니다.
It should be reported to the security department immediately
즉시 보안 부서에 신고해야 합니다.
I'll report it immediately
즉시 신고하겠습니다
You cut off the Internet immediately
너는 즉시 인터넷을 끊어라
yes
예
what happened
무슨 일이에요
half an hour ago
30분 전
Our network firewall
우리의 네트워크 방화벽
Being maliciously attacked
악의적인 공격을 받음
Have you cut off the Internet?
인터넷을 끊으셨나요?
cut off
끊다
Data will not be leaked for the time being
당분간 자료는 유출되지 않습니다
But there is already a problem with the intranet
하지만 이미 인트라넷에 문제가 있습니다.
take us to see
우리를 데리고 보러 가세요
Good here
여기 좋아요
Everyone here
여기 모두들
This is a virus attack
이건 바이러스 공격이에요
I need to find the source of the virus
바이러스의 근원을 찾아야 해요
Use my computer
내 컴퓨터 사용
Please come this way
이쪽으로 와주세요
good
좋은
I suspect there is someone
누군가 있는 것 같아
Hacked into our internal systems
내부 시스템 해킹
Group’s core data
그룹 핵심데이터
Where is it
어디야?
in data center
데이터 센터에서
data center
데이터 센터
Should we
우리는
Go to some core departments and check
일부 핵심 부서에 가서 확인하십시오.
Enter data center maintenance
데이터 센터 유지 관리 시작
Requires personal approval from the Vice President
부사장의 개인 승인이 필요합니다.
Mr. Huang went to a meeting
황 선생님은 회의에 가셨어요
I've reported it to him
나는 그 사람에게 그것을 보고했어요.
request assistance
도움을 요청하다
National security personnel inspection
국가안보인력 점검
All right
괜찮은
follow me
나를 따라와
You lead the way
당신은 길을 인도합니다
Gao Tianyang is just a cover
Gao Tianyang은 단지 표지 일뿐입니다.
attract everyone's attention
모두의 관심을 끌다
He is the real big fish
그 사람이 진짜 큰 물고기야
Taking advantage of Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉(Huang Zicheng)의 활용
When attacking a network
네트워크를 공격할 때
The sample was taken away quietly
샘플은 조용히 치워졌습니다
This plan is perfect
이 계획은 완벽해
need someone now
지금 누군가가 필요해
Bring the sample back
샘플을 다시 가져와
Isn’t it Boss Zhang?
장보스 아닌가요?
She wants to deal with Gao Tianyang
그녀는 Gao Tianyang과 거래하고 싶어합니다
The risk is too great
리스크가 너무 크다
we want to find one
우리는 하나를 찾고 싶어요
Someone who even the National Security Bureau trusts
국가안전보위부도 신뢰하는 사람
Yao Yao
야오야오